everestonline.edu 2014-05-22

# Privacy Policy

Corinthian Colleges, Inc. ("Everest", "we", "us") is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. 

### WHAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION DOES EVEREST COLLECT FROM ME?

Everest collects information in several ways from different parts of our Web sites. We may ask you for personal information, including (but not limited to) when you download a file (such as a .PDF file) from us; when you ask us to contact you; when you join our mailing list; and when you report a problem with one of our sites or services. If you contact Everest, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Everest may also occasionally ask users to complete surveys that we use for research. Wherever Everest collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

Certain of our websites may require registration. Everest may ask for personal information such as your name, email address, age, phone number, gender, zip/postal code, occupation, industry and personal interests.

### Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web sites, which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent to post his/her name prior to posting the testimonial.

### Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct it by resubmitting your request to us with your new contact information. If you no longer desire our service, you may request that we delete/remove such information from our records by contacting us at [privacy@cci.edu](mailto:privacy@cci.edu). We will do our best to respond to your request within 30 days.

### HOW DOES EVEREST USE MY INFORMATION?

Everest's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Web sites, and to service your request. This includes personalization services and interactive communications.

Everest does research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us, or from our server log files. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis to spot trends in our business. Most research revolves around geographical information obtained through a user's address. This helps us to better plan for educational opportunities in our existing markets, as well as potential future markets. We also spot trends to help us assess our product offerings. We closely monitor the time and day that data is submitted to watch for trends in our customer's behavior to help deliver a better web experience.

Everest may also update and supplement personally identifiable information collected from you with other information that we obtain from third parties or from our subsidiaries and affiliates. If we associate information obtained from our affiliates and subsidiaries or third parties with personally identifiable information collected under this policy, we will treat the acquired information like information we have collected ourselves.

We use third parties to assist us in providing services, fulfilling orders and information requests, improving users' experiences on Everest's websites and for other business purposes. Everest will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties for these purposes. When Everest uses agents, contractors or other companies to perform services on its behalf, we will require that they protect your personally identifiable information in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys on our site. If you participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use information collected to monitor company efforts to reach our target audience, as well as to understand how our audience perceives these efforts.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

### Email A Page

If you choose to use our referral service to email a page about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Everest does not store this information. 

### COMMUNICATIONS FROM THE SITE

### Special Offers, Updates and/or Newsletters

We will occasionally send you information on programs that we offer. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice/Opt-out" Section below.

### Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our campus is temporarily closed for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, if you are an active student at one of our schools, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to be added to the Do Not Contact list upon exit from your enrollment in our school, or by emailing [privacy@cci.edu](mailto:privacy@cci.edu)

### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email and also we will contact you by telephone, and in some cases by text message. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email, telephone or text message, in accordance with your wishes. See the "Choice/Opt-out" section below.

### Choice/Opt-out

We never share information with third parties unless we have contracted with them to perform a service for us and they must abide by the terms described above.

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes:

  * If you no longer wish to receive promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by emailing us at [privacy@cci.edu](mailto:privacy@cci.edu). 
  * To stop receiving phone calls, email us at [privacy@cci.edu](mailto:privacy@cci.edu), inform the caller you wished to be placed on our Do Not Call list, or call (866) 786-2765. 
  * To stop receiving text messages, respond to our text with the single word STOP, or email us at [privacy@cci.edu](mailto:privacy@cci.edu). 

###  WHAT ARE COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS AND HOW DOES EVEREST USE THEM? 

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, Everest uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from our web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Generally, we may use cookies to:

(1) Remind us of who you are and to access your information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service. For example, a cookie is set when you register or "Sign In" and is modified when you "Sign Out" of our services.  
(2) Automate certain areas of the Everest web sites or online forms.  
(3) Estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing the Everest website is given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage, usage by a registered user versus by an unregistered user, and to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior.  
(4) Measure certain traffic patterns, which areas of the Everest web site you have visited, and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. We use this research to understand how our users' habits are similar or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on the Everest website a better one. We may use this information to better personalize the content, and promotions that you and other users will see on our sites.  

For some of the reasons listed above Everest does tie personally identifiable information such as your email address to our cookies, for instance if you register to access certain areas of our website. 

Everest also collects IP Addresses, browser information and other computer information to report aggregate information to our marketing department. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. Please refer to your browser's help for further information about your options for controlling or monitoring cookies. 

### Flash LSOs

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences, to that we may personalize your visit by, for example, displaying content based upon what you view on our site.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data, and how it is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118).

### Web Beacons

We and third parties employ on our sites a software technology called Web Beacons, that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Web Beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, Web Beacons are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by Web Beacons to our customers' personally identifiable information.

We also use Web Beacons in outgoing emails to track success of marketing efforts, so we can improve our systems.

We engage a third-party tracking service that uses cookies and Web beacons to track aggregated, non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site, in order to track usage and volume statistics and our web sites.

### WITH WHOM DOES EVEREST SHARE MY INFORMATION

Everest will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or as disclosed in this privacy policy. Everest may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Everest's Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Everest's rights or property, other Everest users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Everest may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

### Service Providers

We use third parties to provide services on our behalf. For example, we use Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding your order. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes.

Everest does not sell or rent user information to anyone except as disclosed in this privacy policy (See "Business Transitions"). We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party other than as provided in this privacy policy, and you will have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service or not to participate in certain promotions or contests.

### Business Transitions

In the event Corinthian Colleges, Inc. (Parent of Everest) goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.

### Links to Other Sites

If you click on a link to a third party site, [including on an advertisement], you will leave the Everest site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as Everest. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to an Everest site, you should read that site's privacy statement before providing any personally identifiable information.

### WHAT ELSE SHOULD I KNOW ABOUT MY PRIVACY

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in instant message or chat areas - that this information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Everest cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

### Children

Our web sites are not intended for anyone under the age of 13. If we find out we have collected information from a child under the age of 13 we will delete that information as soon as reasonably possible.

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we change how we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Privacy   
Corinthian Colleges, Inc   
6 Hutton Centre Drive, Suite 400   
Santa Ana, CA 92618   
Phone: (866) 786-2765
